{
    "id": "f5352dd39f5449a699dc2f260cb2b354",
    "title": "Few, A Few, Little, A Little",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a093e638453c448e854b596e75a27609",
            "title": "Few, A Few, Little, A Little",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I was ………………………… apprehensive about his reaction.",
                    "description": "A little has a positive meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "little",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ………………………. friends that I can trust.",
                    "description": "Use few with plural nouns and little with uncountable nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They were ……………………… concerned about his health.",
                    "description": "Few is used with plural nouns. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "a little",
                        "few",
                        "a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ……………………….. interest in politics.",
                    "description": "Use little with uncountable nouns and few with plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………….. politicians are really honest.",
                    "description": "Either few or a few is possible here with slightly different meanings. Few politicians means hardly any politicians a few politicians means a small number of politicians. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Few",
                        "Little",
                        "A few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There are only …………………………. copies left.",
                    "description": "Write a few after limiting words like only. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like to ask ………………………… questions.",
                    "description": "A few means a small number. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have got …………………………. water if you are thirsty.",
                    "description": "A little indicates a small amount. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "a little",
                        "a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was ………………………… annoyed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "a little",
                        "a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Only ……………………….. students in this class will pass the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I know I have very ……………………….. options.",
                    "description": "Use few after very.",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have very ………………………. money.",
                    "description": "Use little after very. Use little with uncountable things like money. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "a little",
                        "few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}